# Ganesh Narawade WEB DEVELOPER

**PHONE:** 021 02458501

EMAIL: ganesh9211@hotmail.com

PORTFOLIO <a href="https://ganesh9211-dev.github.io/portfolio/">https://ganesh9211-dev.github.io/portfolio/</a>

Visa Status: NZ Permanent Resident

GITHUB: https://github.com/ganesh9211-dev

## Summary

I am a highly motivated, self taught Web Developer with a passion for software development and learning. I embrace challenges, offer diverse experiences, and am an agile learner. I have just completed Industry Connect boot camp which gave me 300 hours of a simulated work environment, where I worked on several apps and learned a lot. I am excited to bring my passion for IT and my positive attitude of making clients happy from my hospitality background to the tech world.

## Skill Highlights

#### **TECHNICAL:**

- Web Development
- User Interface design
- Application Support
- JavaScript (ES6), React.js
- Material UI
- HTML5, CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Node.js, NPM
- RESTful APIs
- SQL databases
- Git, GitHub

#### **PERSONAL:**

- Team player In my previous career, I have been part of diverse teams where team work was paramount.
- Problem Solving I love problem solving and code error finding, I always check logically about errors and deep dive into it to sort it out.
- Fast learner Learned how to build complex designs for my personal projects in a short amount of time.
- Works well under pressure A skill I perfected during my time in the fast-paced environment in the hospitality industry e.g. handled 4 big functions at one time.
- Professional Communication In my previous work environment,good communication was the key asset to have as I had to communicate with different internal departments and fulfil clients requirement professionally for all events success e.g. dealing with International French rugby team management.

## Experience

### **Portfolio**

https://ganesh9211-dev.github.io/portfolio

Full Stack .Net Developer (Intern) MVP Studios, Wellington

March 2019 - August 2019

#### **Talent-Onboarding Project**

Worked as a full stack developer for the Talent project, front end was on ReactJS and Webpack, hosted on Azure.

- Learned full stack web development technologies, including front-end frameworks and SQL databases.
- Attended and contributed to the daily scrums and strategizing the workflow according to the project.
- Introduced state management to the team.
- Writing services for API's (C#, Net)
- Designing the Ul's for the web using React and SemanticUI (bootstrap library for react)
- Gained experience with web technologies such as C# web services architecture, front end technologies (React, Webpack), introduced state management to the team to re-designed the parts of front end and modified services, learned and implemented Agile and SCRUM methodologies.

## **Conference & Events Supervisor**

March 2015 – March 2020

The Rydges Hotel, Wellington

- Efficiency in planning and organising various events and ensure customer satisfaction.
- Assist and direct the team to ensure a high level of service is executed. Strong attention to details.
- Make rosters, order beverages & linen, also plan for the future events.
- Work with Accounting department to track payment to all vendors & service providers.
- Own the planning and delivery for all front of house aspects of the event.
- Actively ensure customer satisfaction through direct interaction with customers
- Generate revenue & wage cost report & send it to Food and beverage Manager on daily basis.
- Proficient working knowledge of computers, Microsoft Excel, Word and Outlook.
- Resolving inter-departmental & staff conflicts.

| Food & Beverage Supervisor (Restaurant & Conference) | September 2013 – March 2015 |
|--|-----------------------------|
| Abel Tasman Hotel, Wellington                        |                             |

| Food & Beverage Supervisor (Restaurant & Conference) | December 2010 – September 2013 |
|--|--------------------------------|
| The Rydges Hotel, Wellington                         |                                |

| Food & Beverage Attendant (Fine Dine Restaurant) | October 2010 – March 2011 |
|--|---------------------------|
| White House Restaurant, Wellington               |                           |

| Food & Beverage Attendant (5 star luxury hotel) | January 2010 – June 2010 |
|---|--------------------------|
| The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, India                   |                          |

| Food & Beverage Attendant (4 star deluxe hotel) | April 2009 – December 2009 |
|---|----------------------------|
| Parabola Restaurant, Rodas Mumbai, India        |                            |

| Food & Beverage Attendant (4 star hotel) | October 2006 – October 2008 |
|--|-----------------------------|
| The Rembrandt Hotel London, UK           |                             |

# Education

| React.js Course                                      | CODE ACADEMY                               | 2020 – 2020          |
|--|--|----------------------|
| JavaScript for beginners' basics Course              | Mosh Courses                               | 2020 – 2020          |
| Software Development Boot Camp course                | INDUTRY CONNECT                            | 2018 - 2019          |
| Bachelor of Hospitality Management degree (level -7) | Wellington Institute of Technology (WelTec | ) <b>2010 - 2011</b> |
| Hospitality Management -Postgraduate Diploma         | London school of Business and Computing    | 2007 - 2008          |
| Hospitality Management -Advanced Diploma             | London school of Business and Computing    | 2006 - 2007          |
| Twin Diploma in Hospitality Management               | Rizvi college of Hotel Management          | 2003 - 2005          |
| References   |  |                      |

## References

| Email: | deshpandelakhan@gmail.com | Email:                  | saurya271@gmail.com |
|--------|---------------------------|-------------------------|---------------------|
| Mobile | no- 022 303 4554          | Mobile no- 0210 313 586 |                     |